Jessica Sulaiman

Jessica.sulaiman86@gmail.com | 276-760-2031 | Philadelphia, PA

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jessicamsulaiman/

Github: https://github.com/jessmeow21

Portfolio: https://jessmeow21.github.io/Portfolio/

Summary

Full stack web developer with a passion and talent to build websites with the user experience in mind. Thought leader in group projects recognized as the creative individual to enhance web appearance and interactivity. Specialized in video production and audio mixing. Attentive to detail and ability to solve problems.

Technical Skills

Programs: Photoshop, Illustrator | Languages: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript | Libraries: Bootstrap, Materialize, jQuery | APIs, JSON | Deployment: Git, Github | Databases: Firebase Spanish language (Conversational), and Social media

Education

University of Pennslyvania, College of Liberal & Professional Studies, Philadelphia, PA Penn LPS Coding Bootcamp Full Stack Flex Program

An intensive 24 week long bootcamp to build dynamic end-to-end web applications. Skills learned consist of HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, and APIs.

Bachelor of Arts in Media Studies and Production | 2015 Temple University, School of Media and Communication, Philadelphia, PA

Experience

Ardmore Toyota, Ardmore, PA Internet Sales Consultant

May 2018 - May 2019

- Provided outstanding customer service and developed rapport with customers
- Supported company CRM and internet sales team
- Converted phone ups and internet leads to sales by making 10 appointments each week

Bradley Communications Corp, Broomall, PA Video Editor/ Technical Assistant

January 2016 - February 2018

- ideo Editor/ Technical Assistant
 - Developed concepts for marketing videos for social media which increased company's online visibility
 - Successfully produced videos for clients which increased sales of more video shoots
 - Produced new sales video for the highest selling program, Quantum Leap which resulted in over 680 people added to the list overnight
 - Cultivated relationships with clients to achieve objectives for their video shoots

Aramark, Philadelphia, PA

June 2015 – January 2016

IT Editor

- Accurately updated internal ticketing system
- Edited metadata and distributed information to vendors
- Performed quality assurance on hundreds of vending sites
- Processed and tracked invoicing of IT projects with Excel and reported errors to PM